KYLE SOKOLIS

PROFILE

Obtain a position with Novetta where I can utilize my data science skills and experience in the United States Navy for data analysis, predictive modeling and supporting company goals while continuing to showcase integrity, innovation and excellence.

EXPERIENCE

FIELD SERVICE ENGINEER, FUJIFILM MEDICAL SYSTEMS – 2016-2018 Primarily responsible for the installation, calibration, inspection, preventive maintenance, troubleshooting, and repair of digital imaging equipment, including electrical, mechanical and software components.

BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING INTERN, CHILDRENS NATIONAL – 2015-2016 Primarily performed preventative and corrective maintenance while professionally conducting interdepartmental communication between the biomedical engineering department and nursing staff for the safe and efficient inventory of 2400+ pumps on site.

DATA CENTER TECHNICIAN LEVEL 2, AMAZON WEB SERVICES – 2013-2014 Installed, configured, maintained and troubleshoot to resolve all Linux OS related issues while coaching junior staff members on standard operating procedures.

SUBMARINE FIRE CONTROL TECHNICIAN, UNITED STATES NAVY – 2008-2013 Experienced with linux-based systems in a tactical weapons computer work center on a national strategic asset. Facilitated change management projects and managed quality assurance documentation and tasks.

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY DATA SCIENCE IMMERSIVE – 2019 UNITED STATES NAVY, FIRE CONTROL TECHNICIAN – 2013

CLEARANCE

Previously held TS/SCI while attached to USS Maryland SSBN 738 Blue Crew submarine.

SKILLS

Python - Pandas - NumPy - SciPy - SQL - Data Cleaning/Exploration - Machine Learning
Regression/Classification - Scikit-Learn - Statsmodels - Natural Language Processing
SpaCy - NLTK - Webscraping/Data Mining - Requests - BeautifulSoup - Hadoop
Matplotlib - Seaborn - Data Visualization/Analysis